Down here!
My Harmon will hit you all the harder!
Underwater...
turquoise blue...
OVERDRIVE!
He did it! Bravo!
That was amazing!
It's not over yet!
I can't believe Bluford was able
to dodge that blast of Harmon.
He moved so fast underwater.
He was all a blur.
My overdrive barely
clansed off his forehead.
Now I know anything
less than a solid punch
won't be enough to send
the Hormone into him.
My good Lord Dio, I thank
thee for this life anew,
that I may duel with
this stout-hearted lad.
My heart would swell to
bursting if it still beats.
In blood and deed, he
is the stuff of heroes.
Now we will fight in our native element.
It is by mastery of our arts and strength
of our spirits that we wage this duel.
Bear your soul.
Hold nothing back lest you not
survive beyond this moment.
Even as Dio's puppet, his pride
is a force to be reckoned with.
But his knightly valor has been
twisted into a wanton love of violence.
When I best you, I'll take
your head as my trophy.
It's easy to let your hair do the work.
Come, withstand my hormone
face to face like a man.
Let's go.
I'm going to build a way
of the power of the earth.
If you are finding the way of
the world, the path of the world!
I'm going to be a boy.
I'm going to live with the land.
I'm going
to live with
the path of the world.
I'm going to live with
the heart of the world.
Overtry Barrage!
Jojo!
This is terrible.
Harmon can only be projected
through the arms and the legs.
With his arms bound in
front of him like that,
he has no way of blasting through
that infernal hair of Bluford's.
I...
I want to help him out, but you
and me have got things even worse.
I think old Tarkus fancies a dust-up.
His hair, it's tearing through
my clothes, through my skin.
The more I struggle, the tighter it
winds, and it's sucking my blood away.
Beat your petty life adieu,
behold the coup de grace!
I'll take your head and bathe in
a fountain of life-giving blood!
Take this!
Watts is not all that conducts
hormones, Metal Silver Overdrive!
What a brain!
Using his sword to hoist Bluford by his
own bleeding petard, Who thinks of that?
How my heart resonates.
I'm pulsing with heat and life.
My very blood is a symphony within me.
Sunlight, yellow, overdrive!
There we go, that's it.
About time we heard the
welcome crackle of Harmon.
When I pummeled Bluford a moment
ago, something felt different.
Knowing his past makes his
present corruption all the worse.
Take heart, Jojo.
He is that man no longer.
He's nothing but a zombie,
eager to spread his evil.
You must be the one to end him.
Boy, I'm the Black Knight, Bluford.
Strike me as thou wilt.
This pain is nothing.
He's still dangerous, mate!
Look out!
He's been missing an arm
and scorched all the hell.
He's laying into Jojo
every bit as ferociously.
What the?
Don't just stand there!
Do something!
If you don't get out of there
now, it's curtains for you!
Have they both gone mad?
What are they doing, huh?
A moment to go.
You said this pain is nothing.
That means pain is something
you can feel again.
Oh, the flowers.
They're blooming all around him.
Even now, the hormone ravages the evil
that animates Bluford's long-dead corpse.
You see the long forgotten pain came
back only humans know that sort of ache.
Observe my dear Speed
Wagon his zombie body
succumbs to the hormone but his noble soul
is redeemed in the
process I could sense the
good in you that's why
I didn't try to dodge
You could have killed me just now but
you stayed your hand look at his face
it's like all the rage and hatred he
had when Dio brought him back are gone.
His features are so gentle he could be a
bloke catching up with his oldest mate.
You stood there like a statue,
ready to take the fatal blow.
Oblivion beckoned, but you
put your trust in me.
Your faith in human goodness is rare.
One side have railed
against the pain I feel.
Now, going to my rightful
end, I cherish all
that proves me human.
It gives me joy.
The embers dull within
me, but I am tranquil.
There
is no bitterness left.
What irony to live yet again,
dying with thanks on my lips for
the very man who slaughters me anew.
I shall return to my one true master.
I would know The name of
the warrior who bested me
would you kindly do me that
honor it's jonathan joestar?
Sir Jonathan I leave you
this sword given to me
by my precious queen and
the word engraved upon it
Luck but first let me affix my
own benediction pluck sir bluefoot
Go you to your rest.
Let no one doubt you
have earned it, Bluford.
Why?
Why did I have to strike
him down to redeem his soul?
He died once before with hate in his
heart, but his spirit was still pure.
He returned not out of choice,
but dragged above by Dio's evil.
His evil in the mosque's power.
I will send them both
to hell before the dawn.
Jojo!
He's right behind you!
Tarkus!
You villain!
That was the armor of a
steadfast friend and comrade!
He died with honor and dignity!
He died like a spineless dog!
He was too clever by half, liked
winning his fights with thinking.
I just hit him until they fall to pieces!
What use have I got for clever?
I carry a sword as tall as a man!
None of you will get an easy death.
Jojo, nice catch.
The cliff is crumbling.
These dead leaves. Jojo. Yes, sir.
My magnetism, overdrive!
Hurry, Poco!
Speedwagon, grab on!
All human beings, whether
adept at Hamon or not,
constantly exude a weak magnetic field.
An overdrive can increase
the power of that field.
Jojo and Zeppeli sent it into the leaves,
drawing them together into a solid sheet.
Wow! Bye!
We're flying!
I can't believe it!
I bet you're magicians, huh?
You'd have to be, right?
How did you learn to do all of these
neat spells in the first place?
Damn good question!
I've been watching them do
it and I still pinch myself.
Oi, Baron, what's the story?
We're not going anywhere.
How on earth did you pick
up all this mumbo-jumbo?
Many years ago, my travels took me to
India, where I discovered a mysterious man.
He called himself a doctor,
though he was very young and
lacked all the tools of the trade.
Little did I know, he was more potent
of a medic than I'd ever encountered.
He took a gangrenous limb in his hands
and healed it with light from within.
That was the day I learned of Hamon.
I'd been looking for something with
which to fight the stone mask's evil,
and in Hamon, I had found it.
Eager to learn,
I crossed into Tibet
and up the Salween River
in search of he who had
taught the young healer.
His name was Tonpetty.
Stranger, these eyes of
mine have seen your future.
If you pursue the mysteries of Harmon
as my pupil, your fate is sealed.
The day will come when this
will be the death of you.
I understand.
If I must die to end this quest, so be it.
Master Tonpedi's prophecy is never far
from my mind, but I cannot tell them.
Not even Jojo.
Baron?
So, that sound?
That's part of Halmon
doing its thing, yeah?
Hardly.
Look out, it's Tarkus!
He's insane, leaping from that height
just to give chase to his foes.
There's a goodly amount of Hormone
holding these leaves together, you brute.
Painful to the touch for the United.
What's that?
That's where the Knights used
to train in the olden days.
Lead to safety, everyone.
Before we get swatted out of the sky.
Crazy Blighter, he just slammed
himself straight into the tower!
Yes, and thank your lucky
stars that he did Speedwagon.
Unlike their master Dio's
minions can't regenerate
so that should be the
last we see of that beast?
How did...
he should be mincemeat?
Even in death, he has a will of iron.
How does his body endure
under such punishment?
He's climbing up!
We can't destroy Dio while
this monster dogs our steps.
It seems we have no other choice.
Tarkus meets his doom here and now.
Jojo, this will be perilous.
Get the lad to safety within.
This door.
Something's odd about it.
Be careful.
This is where they used to train
the knights how to kill people.
They say it's full of booby traps.
Doc Jojo!
Something's coming at you!
Jojo!
Who ensnared me?
Sorokas!
Yes, caught you good.
Your fleet of foot, little man.
But now you and me are
chained to each other.
You've got nowhere to run.
Jojo had wandered into the
lair of the Two-Headed Dragon,
an ancient sparring ground and
home of the Chain Deathmatch.
I killed 48 men here.
Taking a life's an art
form, and I'm a master.
That's enough.
You can't punch through it.
That door is solid iron.
Goodness, he's batted his
knuckles bloody against it.
Harmon is very versatile,
but it's meant to be used as a
rapier, not as a sledgehammer.
Bricks I could beat to a powder,
but this door is too strong.
Jojo faces a darker dilemma.
That chain about his neck is more
than ripple energy can overcome.
Breaking out of that collar is impossible,
and you'll need the key to unlock it.
Too bad it's right here.
During a deathmatch, the door to the
outside is fashioned to lock tight.
Just as I have the key to your collar,
you have the one that goes to mine.
Therefore, the only way that either
of us is going to get out of here
is by taking the other's head!
Come on!
Overdrive!
The chain is touching the stone ceiling,
so the Hormone lacks a
direct path into Taruchus.
He's broken the bone in my forearm.
It's a simple thing to fix.
A little Hormone and I'm good as new.
But in order to use Hormone, I need
to be free of this damnable collar.
I can't breathe.
Jojo!
Oh no, this is all so frightening.
I think I wet myself.
This village was safe
until these men arrived.
I'm in danger here.
You need to get away from all this
fighting with the double Pogo.
I see a lever, Baron Zeppeli.
No telling for certain, but I think
pulling on it will open this door.
Fighting Tarkus is a daunting
enough task as it is,
never mind doing it fresh out
of a battle with Blueford.
Come, hella high water.
We must find a way to get
in there and help him.
It's locked up tighter than a nunnery.
It's so narrow.
Try as they might, they
could never squeeze through.
But...
Maybe I could.
Blast it!
We could batter this door
till Judgment Day to no avail!
We'll have to use the
cliffside entrance Tarkus used!
But that'll take too much time!
Time that he don't got!
I know, but we've no other choice!
Always on the bleeding sidelines!
I'm powerless, there's
nothing I can do to help.
Look at me, brat, I'm talking to you!
I said look at me, are you stupid or what?
He's such a little scary cat.
What a baby, he's shaking like a leaf!
Look, fellas, look at him.
Oh is the baby going to cry?
Hey, look.
Come on, let's get out of here!
Sis, it's you?
Poco, really?
You're letting those boys bully you again?
They do this all the time Why not
try standing up to them for once?
I'll bloody their noses!
I will When? Tomorrow? In a year?
I don't know
Poco, what frightens you
more than anything else?
I know that hurt, but
you're still in one piece.
Pain's not the worst thing.
There's something far worse.
It's growing up being too
afraid to do anything.
What kind of a life would that be?
I'm sorry, sis.
It's all right, Poco.
Let's get you home into
some clean clothes.
Poco!
A window!
Oi, lad!
That's brave, but going in
there's gonna be the end of ya!
Speedwagon, get the boy down!
A butcher like Tarkus
doesn't care who he kills!
He'll crush Pogo underfoot like a bug!
Come on now!
Enough of this nonsense, Pogo!
Just think of what's gonna happen to
Winnight's Lot if these monsters win.
If that Jojo guy gets killed in
here, they'll attack us next.
What if they hurt Sis?
I have to keep her safe, no matter what.
Paces!
I'm standing up to them now!
Stay back!
He'll kill you!
Do not interfere, you brat!
Poco!
It hurt a lot, but I'm still
in one piece, so it's fine.
I was brave, huh?
Brave as a bear, my lad.
Take heart.
It's nothing that won't heal.
Get him, Baron, go!
Give that hulking bastard the what for!
Zeppeli?
The day will come when this
will be the death of you.
In fine, is tonight the
night that I go to my grave.
Fate is a fickle mistress,
but I cannot deny her.
Zeppeli!
Why do you sound so dire?
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Cold in morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
And around the lake.
Mountains come out of the sky.
And they stand there.
One mile over, we'll be
there and we'll see you.
Ten and two summers, we'll be
there and I'll be with you.
Twenty, four, five mile
over, we'll see you.
I'll be there with you.
This bloody savagery is unbelievable!
Oh no! Tarkus!
Pathetic waste of flesh! Jojo! Take it!
Make it yours!